# MUHAMMAD GANJAR IMANUDIN

Gelatik Dalam No.402/151 A Bandung · (+62)896-2310-8356 emailmganjar@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/muhganjar/ · berpergian.vercel.app

Software developer with more than two years' experience in developing scalable web application. Having experience focused develop in back-end side and would jump any opportunity to continue growing my skills in back-end side.

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### FEBRUARY 2022 - PRESENT

## **BACK-END PROGRAMMER, PT. AGATE INTERNATIONAL**

- Develop back-end side for a B2B project using .NET Core 5 with team of 6 programmers
- Focused on communicate with other system and providing data to front-end side
- Setup and configure scheduled background job for automatic task

#### **DECEMBER 2019 – JANUARY 2022**

## FULL-STACK WEB PROGRAMMER, PT. AGATE INTERNATIONAL

- Develop front-end admin dashboard for gamified learning apps and back-end its systems using Ruby on Rails with team of 5 programmers
- Develop REST API for communicate between back-end and front-end application using Grape (a framework API for Ruby)
- Maintained systems for 5 different clients

#### **JULY 2017 - JANUARY 2018**

## FRONT-END PROGAMMER, PT. CIPTADRA SOFTINDO

- Design and develop admin dashboard for city government using Phalcon as front-end & Bootstrap as CSS framework.
- Design and develop mobile version of admin dashboard in Android using web-view

## **BACK-END PROJECTS**

#### JANUARY 2022 - PRESENT

## **GAME PROJECT, PT. AGATE INTERNATIONAL**

- Base project using C# and .NET Core 5 for develop API
- Developed the backend for a Unity game project, integrating with the game to save data to the database using MongoDB for multi-region support
- Using Kubernetes for automatic deploying and scaling instance of running apps across multiple regions

Last Update: 10th December 2024

#### FEBRUARY 2022 - DECEMBER 2022

## **B2B PROJECT, PT. AGATE INTERNATIONAL**

- Base project using C# and .NET 5 framework for develop API
- Application developed in monolith and written with MVC architecture
- Using Kubernetes for automatic deploying and scaling instance of running apps
- Automatic task on background job using Hangfire.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **SEPTEMBER 2019**

# SARJANA TERAPAN KOMPUTER (S.TR.KOM.), POLITEKNIK NEGERI BANDUNG

- Diploma 4, Informatic Engineering with GPA 3.03/4.00
- Member of HIMAKOM (Himpunan Mahasiswa Komputer) POLBAN
- 4<sup>th</sup> Place Cluster 2 Competitive Programming (Informatics Department only)

## **SKILLS**

- C#
- .NET (5-8)
- Ruby
- Rails

- PostgreSQL
- Git
- MongoDB
- Kubernetes

Last Update: 10<sup>th</sup> December 2024